That our children want to be like us from the very beginning, they want to
look like us, they
want to keep a moustache like us, they
want to talk like us, they
want to eat what
we eat, they want to drink what we drink, they do what we do, they
sit like us, they behave like us, whether it is a fast
or a meal, our children wanted to be like us, on
this are we showing the right thing to our children,
ICICI Lombard has brought
brother-sister sitting hand in hand
with mother for your children, if not for yourself then adopt the
right habit for them because we know that it is
more
precious to you than your own life, Ajay has happened in the life of your children.